Hubungi

Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia bahrulrozak13062001@gmail.c om

www.linkedin.com/in/bahrul-rozak (LinkedIn) github.com/Bahrul-Rozak (Personal) bahrul-rozak.github.io/bahrulrozak/ (Portfolio)

Keahlian Teratas

Front-end Development Ubuntu

Full-Stack Development

Languages

Bahasa Inggris (Limited Working)
Bahasa Indonesia (Native or
Bilingual)

Bahasa Sunda (Limited Working)

Certifications

Front-End Web dan Back-End Web SIB Batch 2 bersama Dicoding

Google Analytics

Menjadi Front-End Web Developer Expert

Cybersecurity

TEMA PELATIHAN
PROGRAMMING: HTML, CSS,
JAVASCRIPT

Honors-Awards

3rd Winner UI/UX Design

Pemateri

Publications

Implementasi Business Intelligence untuk Menganalisis Data Jumlah Sarana Kesehatan Provinsi Kaltim Tahun 2016 - 2020

Mobile First Approach Guide [E - Book]

Bahrul Rozak

Front End Engineer | Mentor | Technical Writter

Kota Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia

Ringkasan

Assalamualaikum! Merhaba!

As an experienced Web Developer from Indonesia, I have the ability to build websites using cutting-edge technologies such as the Codelgniter, Laravel, and Vue.js frameworks. I have both individual and team working experience, allowing me to efficiently and effectively complete tasks and projects. My current focus is on improving my skills as a Front End Developer by learning new technologies and participating in open source projects. Additionally, I have a hobby of sharing my knowledge of programming through Github. I am confident that my skills and experience, along with my passion for sharing knowledge, will be highly valuable in helping a company or team achieve their goals.

Regards

Bahrul Rozak - Student from University of Muhammadiyah Prof. DR. HAMKA

Pengalaman

BPTI UHAMKA

Web Developer

Oktober 2021 - Present (1 tahun 5 bulan)

- Developed the uhamka.ac.id website using Codeigniter and MySQL
- Developed the teknoka website using Codeigniter and MySQL
- Developed the ICNSSE website using Codeigniter and MySQL
- Performed Search Engine Optimization to improve rank alongside the team
- Developed to assist team members in creating internal applications using Laravel, Microsoft SQL Server

and VueJS

- Participated in the Search Engine Optimization to improve rank as part of the team.

RS Daan Mogot KesDam

Pharmacy Intern

Oktober 2018 - Oktober 2018 (1 bulan)

Kota Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia

- Compounding medication according to doctor's request
- Providing medication information to patients in accordance with standard operating procedures
- Regularly checking pharmacy inventory.

RSUD Kota Tangerang

Pharmacy Intern

April 2017 - April 2017 (1 bulan)

Tangerang, Banten, Indonesia

- Compounding medication according to doctor's request
- Providing medication information to patients in accordance with standard operating procedures
- Regularly checking pharmacy inventory.

Pendidikan

Universitas Muhammadiyah Prof. Dr. Hamka Student, Teknik Informatika · (2019 - 2023)

SMK Kesehatan Bina Prestasi Tangerang

Farmasi/Apotek · (2017 - 2019)